<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Advice on John-Henry Pezzuto</title>
    <link>/tags/advice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Advice on John-Henry Pezzuto</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/advice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>In Defense of the One Punch Man Workout</title>
      <link>/post/in-defense-of-the-one-punch-man-workout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/in-defense-of-the-one-punch-man-workout/</guid>
      <description>The second season of &amp;ldquo;One Punch Man&amp;rdquo; is coming out pretty soon! For those uninitiated, One Punch Man is a Japanese super hero anime making fun of super heroes. The show makes fun plays on the over-the-topness of super heroes but also the beaurocracy, the public relations struggles of being a superhero (much like The first Incredibles movie). What sets this show apart is that it also manages to have genuinely cool action scenes, and be laugh out loud funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redefining the Vocabulary of Everyday Life</title>
      <link>/post/redefining-the-vocabulary-of-everyday-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/redefining-the-vocabulary-of-everyday-life/</guid>
      <description>Easily the most profound ideas from modern clinical psychology is cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT). For those unfamiliar, the key tenet of CBT is that if we can change the way we think, then we can change the way we feel. In practice, CBT involves learning to recognize distortions in thinking, and then address these issues with new improved practices. For example, people often use the word &amp;ldquo;should&amp;rdquo; in everyday life. &amp;ldquo;You should focus on school&amp;rdquo;; &amp;ldquo;You shouldn’t eat so much junk food&amp;rdquo;; &amp;ldquo;You should be grateful for this opportunity&amp;rdquo; etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Levitt’s Graduate School Advice</title>
      <link>/post/steve-levitt-s-advice-about-graduate-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/steve-levitt-s-advice-about-graduate-school/</guid>
      <description>When I lived at Chicago I was able to catch up Steve Levitt with a small group of students talk about his opinions on going to graduate school. His advice was tailored towards economics students, but I think other people will may find it valuable as well.
He started by saying that our presumption that being a professor at a top school is correct. Being a top professor is indeed a awesome job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Writing Book Recommended by Larry McEnerney (Director of the University of Chicago’s Writing Program)</title>
      <link>/post/the-writing-books-recommended-by-larry-mcenerney-director-of-the-university-of-chicago-s-writing-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-writing-books-recommended-by-larry-mcenerney-director-of-the-university-of-chicago-s-writing-program/</guid>
      <description>One day during the Spring quarter I was early to my writing class and found myself standing next to Larry McEnerney, director of the University of Chicago&amp;rsquo;s writing program. I had never spoken to early personally before that day, but I knew he was fairly famous on campus for having a fabulous, quirky personality, and was considered by many students to be a genius. I mustered up the up to courage to ask him if he had any writing books to recommend.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>