<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guides on John-Henry Pezzuto</title>
    <link>/tags/guides/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Guides on John-Henry Pezzuto</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>An Overview of Statistics for the Social Sciences</title>
      <link>/post/an-overview-of-statistics-for-the-science-sciences/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/an-overview-of-statistics-for-the-science-sciences/</guid>
      <description>I found myself deeply inspired by the Edward Tufte tweet where he recommmends adding a warning label to statistical techniques:
If use of every statistical model was accompanied warnings similar to those accompanying every prescription drug. In medical research, mistakes in data analysis can shorten 1000s of lives. #biostatistics #statistics #datascience pic.twitter.com/GhLltkd3NG
&amp;mdash; Edward Tufte (@EdwardTufte) June 24, 2018   I don&amp;rsquo;t know of anything like this that currently exists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 1 - A Beginner’s Guide to Healthy Eating (Creating a Shopping List)</title>
      <link>/post/a-beginner-s-guide-to-healthy-eating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/a-beginner-s-guide-to-healthy-eating/</guid>
      <description>Background After seeing this meme about myself I realized it might be a good time to make some lifestyle changes. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fairly active and of a healthy weight, so I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen healthy eating as a pressing issue, but in the pursuit of perfection, I think healthy eating is a good goal to aspire to, if only as a challenge.
One thing I noticed is that my biggest barrier is that I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to cook, or what to buy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>notes on writing</title>
      <link>/post/notes-on-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/notes-on-writing/</guid>
      <description>productivity in writing https://theresearchwhisperer.wordpress.com/2018/07/10/should-we-really-write-daily/ hese were: time blocking, artificial deadlines, seeking ‘flow’, incremental step setting, accountability structures and using ‘freewriting’ as an unblocking technique.
abstract They expect to see the warrant and the contribution made clear
TOC needs to be clear, totally clear.
methods https://theresearchwhisperer.wordpress.com/2015/03/10/writing-research-methods/
specify specifics. justify exactly why. explain how it brings you closer to what you&amp;rsquo;re trying to do. clear rationale why this analysis will achieve objective of project</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>