<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Productivity on John-Henry Pezzuto</title>
    <link>/tags/productivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Productivity on John-Henry Pezzuto</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>notes on writing</title>
      <link>/post/notes-on-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/notes-on-writing/</guid>
      <description>productivity in writing https://theresearchwhisperer.wordpress.com/2018/07/10/should-we-really-write-daily/ hese were: time blocking, artificial deadlines, seeking ‘flow’, incremental step setting, accountability structures and using ‘freewriting’ as an unblocking technique.
abstract They expect to see the warrant and the contribution made clear
TOC needs to be clear, totally clear.
methods https://theresearchwhisperer.wordpress.com/2015/03/10/writing-research-methods/
specify specifics. justify exactly why. explain how it brings you closer to what you&amp;rsquo;re trying to do. clear rationale why this analysis will achieve objective of project</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Hide the Cursor on Mac and How to Fix Cursorcerer</title>
      <link>/post/how-to-hide-the-cursor-on-mac-and-how-to-fix-cursorcerer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/how-to-hide-the-cursor-on-mac-and-how-to-fix-cursorcerer/</guid>
      <description>My mac used to hide the cursor by pressing F6 (fn F6 for those uninitiatied). Then one update, I don&amp;rsquo;t know, Apple took that feature out? Anyway the best work around I found thus far was to download Cursorcerer, which is a freeware program which basically offers the same function with a couple extra features.
However, I noticed if I don&amp;rsquo;t use Cursorcerer for awhile it stops working. Because of this, I made an applescript that toggles it on and off which is much faster (and much less annoying) than going to my settings and toggling the Cursorcerer manually.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>